mypcbusiness.com 2012-11-25

# MyPCBusiness - Privacy Policy

MyPCBusiness Privacy Policy

We're serious about online privacy, and have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. This page outlines our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of user information.

What information does MyPCBusiness collect from visitors?

MyPCBusiness collects information from our visitors and users of our website and uses the information for marketing and administration purposes, in the fulfillment of our service commitment to you, or as required under the law.

As a user of this website, MyPCBusiness may collect your personally identifiable information when you subscribe to the MyPCBusiness service. The information that we collect is limited to your name, email address and other contact information.

Why is information collected?

Information may be collected in an effort to enhance your user experience, provide you with information regarding MyPCBusiness services, and/or to provide you with the products and/or services that you request.

We, or our authorized third-party affiliates, may also collect general information about transactions as they correspond to our advertisements, products and services. This aggregate information may include various types of demographic and usage information, but 

_does not include personally identifiable information_

.

This information is used in an aggregated manner to determine advertising effectiveness and is sometimes shared with our advertising partners for the same limited purpose.

How does MyPCBusiness protect my information?

We have implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personally identifiable information. Users' personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by certain key employees.

Should it be necessary to transmit your personally identifiable information to a reputable third party vendor to fulfill our service commitment to you, MyPCBusiness will require all recipients of such information to maintain it as confidential, use the information for the limited and intended purpose and agree not to disclose such information.

Will MyPCBusiness disclose the information it collects to others?

MyPCBusiness does not rent, sell or share any of the information collected by this site with unrelated 3rd-parties, except when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

1\. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights;

2\. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action in conjunction with illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MyPCBusiness's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law;

3\. We are required by law to provide the IRS with Tax ID numbers and/or other personally identifiable information about Affiliates located in the U.S. who promote MyPCBusiness and earn over $600 in commissions in a calender year.

4\. We are required by law to provide the IRS with Tax ID numbers and/or other personally identifiable information about User Testers located in the U.S. who receive over $600 in payments from MyPCBusiness in a calender year.

Does MyPCBusiness use "cookies" or pixel "tags"?

Cookies are bits of information that a website can transfer to a visitor's browser to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. Cookies allow website owners to better customize a site to your individual preferences.

The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and most major websites use them. We may use cookies to help provide you with a better experience on our site; however, we do not store personally identifying information in cookies.

Like many Web sites, MyPCBusiness may also use pixel tags, also known as beacons, spotlight tags or web bugs, to improve our understanding of site traffic, visitor behavior, and response to promotional and advertising campaigns, as a supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement.

We may also implement pixel tags provided by other companies, and limit the collection of information for the same purpose. We do not store personally identifying information in pixel tags.

Can I access or modify the Personal Identifying Information collected?

You can view and/or modify the information provided to us at any time by logging in to your account, and clicking the "Profile" link. You may also submit your request to modify your account information via any of the methods below.

What if I want to Opt-Out of email communications from MyPCBusiness?

MyPCBusiness provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future promotional communications from us.

You may do so in the following ways. Please note however that even if you opt-out, you may still receive important announcements or updates regarding your MyPCBusiness account unless you cancel your account.

1\. Email: [support@mypcbusiness.com](mailto:support@mypcbusiness.com?subject=&cc=&bcc=&body=)  
  
2\. Website: http://www.mypcbusiness.com/cancel.cgi  
  
3\. Postal Mail: MyPCBusiness, LLC, 453 E. Wonderview Ave. Suite 126, Estes Park, CO 80517

Can children or minors use MyPCBusiness?

MyPCBusiness does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from or about anyone under the age of 18. If we discover we have received such information in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately.

If you believe MyPCBusiness has any information from or about anyone under the age of 18, please contact us. If you are under 18, you may use MyPCBusiness only under the supervision of a parent or guardian.

Links to Other Sites

This website may contain links to other sites, and we want you to know that MyPCBusiness is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

Your consent

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide per this Privacy Policy. We also reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. Should this be necessary, we will post any changes here so that you're always aware of the information that we collect and how we may or may not intend to use it.

Contacting MyPCBusiness

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy statement, the privacy-related practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us via one of the methods above.

This Privacy Policy was last updated June 12, 2012.
